<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ThalassaemiaApp</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">2031797653740303</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb2031797653740303</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about_content"> Foundation Against Thalassaemia (Regd.) is an NGO registered under Indian Societies
        Act 1860/21, working for the Care and Welfare of thalassaemic children since 1995, with a vision to make India
        Thalassaemia Free.\n\nThalassaemia is a life threatening inherited blood disorder wherein the body cannot make healthy
        haemoglobin and the person is dependent on regular blood transfusions, at an interval of every 15-21 days, throughout
        life to survive.\n\nIt is disheartening that India is the Thalassaemia capital of the world with 50 million thalassaemia
        carriers and over 1,25,000 thalassaemia majors. Every year, approximately 100,000 children with Thalassaemia Major are
        born world over, of which 10-12% are born in India.\n\nOur Foundation provides free care to about 200 thalassaemic
        children registered with us from Delhi NCR and farther areas of North India.  This involves providing free medicines,
        blood and blood transfusion set-up, regular health check-ups by doctors from reputed Hospitals and other activities like
        organising trips, painting competitions, cultural programs, skill development courses, meetings with celebrities etc.
        for their physical and psychological welfare and to make them self dependent. The average monthly expense for each such
        child is INR 7,500-10,000 (US$ 110 - 125).\n\nOur objective is that every individual must be aware if he/she is a
        thalassaemia carrier, to save a lifelong of pain and trauma for a child. And, our Mission is to *Make India Thalassaemia
        Free by 2025*. This mission can be achieved only by creating mass level education and awareness and motivating people to
        go for Thalassaemia Carrier (HbA2) screening during pre-marital, pre-conception or early-pregnency stages.\n\nOur
        organization has endorsements, patronage and moral support from some of India's top personalities like Hon'ble President
        of India Shri Ram Nath Kovind, late Dr  APJ Abdul Kalam, Shri Pranab Mukherjee, Smt Pratibha Patil, ex-Prime Minister
        Dr. Manmohan Singh, Bollywood star Karishma Kapoor, Iconic Cricket Stars Kapil Dev, Virender Sehwag, Bhajan Samrat
        Narender Chanchal, etc. to name a few.\n\nWe are a Member of Thalassaemia International Federation and have also been
        granted exemption by Indian Government Us 80G of Income tax Act 1961.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="thalassaemia_content"><b>What is Thalassaemia ?</b>\n\n

Thalassaemia (originated from Greek words  is an inherited blood disorder that causes your body to make less haemoglobin or abnormal
        haemoglobin. Haemoglobin helps red blood cells spread oxygen through your body. Low levels of haemoglobin may cause anaemia,
        an illness that makes you feel weak and tired. Severe anemia can damage organs and lead to death.\n\n

There are two main types:\n
Alpha and Beta. Beta thalassaemia is the most common.

\n\n<b>Beta thalassaeemia</b>\n\n
You need both alpha and beta globin to make haemoglobin. Beta thalassaemia occurs when one or both of the two genes that make
        beta-globin don\'t work or only partly work as they should.\n\n

If you have one damaged gene, you may have mild anaemia and probably won\'t need treatment. This is called beta thalassaemia minor or beta thalassaemia trait. It happens when you get a normal gene from one parent and a thalassaemia gene from the other.

\n\nWhen both genes are damaged, it means you got a thalassaemia gene from each parent. You may have moderate or severe anemia.

\n\nIf you have moderate anemia (beta thalassaemia intermedia), you may need blood transfusions.

\n\nPeople with severe anemia (called beta thalassaemia major or Cooley\'s anemia) need blood transfusions throughout life. Symptoms of anemia usually begin within a few months after birth.

\n\n<b>Alpha thalassaemia</b>\n\n

This type occurs when one or more of the four alpha-globin genes that make haemoglobin are missing or damaged.\n\n

If one gene is missing or damaged: Your red blood cells might be smaller than normal. You will have no symptoms and you
        will not need treatment. But you are a silent carrier. This means you don\'t have the disease but can pass the defective gene to your child.

\n\nIf two genes are missing or damaged: You will have very mild anaemia that will typically not need treatment. This is called alpha thalassaemia minor or alpha thalassaemia trait.

\n\nIf three genes are missing: You will have mild to moderately severe anemia. This is sometimes called hemoglobin H disease. If it is severe, you may need blood transfusions.

\n\nIf all four genes are missing: This is called alpha thalassaemia major or hydrops fetalis. The fetus will be still-born, or the child will die soon after birth.

\n\nA defect in one or more genes causes thalassaemia.

\n\nIf you, either parent, or any of your siblings have thalassaemia or carry a gene for thalassaemia and you\'re thinking about having a child, you may want to talk to a genetic counselor before you get pregnant. A genetic counselor can tell you how likely it is that your child will have the disease and how severe it might be.
    \n</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">default</string>
    <string name="title_activity_thalassaemics_reg">ThalassaemicsReg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notifications">NotificationsActivity</string>
    <string name="support_us_content">Our Foundation provides free care to about 200 thalassaemic
        children registered with us from Delhi NCR and farther areas of North India.  This involves providing free medicines,
        blood and blood transfusion set-up, regular health check-ups by doctors from reputed Hospitals and other activities like
        organising trips, painting competitions, cultural programs, skill development courses, meetings with celebrities etc.
        for their physical and psychological welfare and to make them self dependent. The average monthly expense for each such
        child is INR 7,500-10,000 (US$ 100 - 125).\n\nSponsor a Thalassaemic Child\'s Care and Welfare for as little as Rs
        5,100/- per month:\n\nMedicines: Rs 5,100/-\nComplete Care and Welfare: Rs 11,000/-\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login1">LoginActivity1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="home_content">Foundation Against Thalassaemia (Regd.), is an NGO registered under Indian Societies
        Act 1860/21, working for the Care and Welfare of thalassaemic children since 1995, with a vision to make India
        Thalassaemia Free.</string>
    <string name="thali_quote">Let\'s help India become Thalassaemia Free by 2025.</string>



</resources>
